[
    {
        "option1": "I was not able to doing this work.",
        "option2": "I was not being able to did this work.",
        "option3": "I was not being able to do this work.",
        "option4": "I was not able to do this work.",
        "question": "আমি এই কাজটা পারছিলাম না",
        "correct": 3,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
        "option1": "We should love to all.",
        "option2": "We love should to all.",
        "option3": "We shall love all.",
        "option4": "We should love all.",
        "question": "আমাদের সবাইকে ভালোবাসা উচিৎ",
        "correct": 4,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
        "option1": "Should what you do ?",
        "option2": "What should you to do ?",
        "option3": "Should you do what ?",
        "option4": "What should you do ?",
        "question": "তোমার কি করা উচিৎ ?",
        "correct": 4,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
        "option1": "Shreya should sing not less than three songs.",
        "option2": "Shreya should not sing more than three songs.",
        "option3": "Shreya should not sing less than three songs.",
        "option4": "Shreya should sing not more than three songs.",
        "question": "শ্রেয়ার তিনটে গানের চেয়ে কম গাওয়া উচিৎ নয়",
        "correct": 3,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
        "option1": "Which things should you take with you ?",
        "option2": "Which which things should you take with you ?",
        "option3": "Should you take which which things with you ?",
        "option4": "Which things should you to take with you ?",
        "question": " তোমাদের কী কী জিনিশ সঙ্গে নিয়ে যাওয়া উচিৎ ?",
        "correct": 1,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
        "option1": "Sudip must will buy a phone.",
        "option2": "Sudip must to buy a phone.",
        "option3": "Sudip must buy a phone.",
        "option4": "Sudip must buys a phone.",
        "question": "সুদীপ ফোন কিনতে বাধ্য",
        "correct": 3,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
        "option1": "Sudip has to buys a phone.",
        "option2": "Sudip must has to buy a phone.",
        "option3": "Sudip has to buy a phone.",
        "option4": "Sudip has buy a phone.",
        "question": "সুদীপকে ফোন কিনতেই হবে",
        "correct": 3,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
        "option1": "Do have you to return today ?",
        "option2": "Will you return on today ?",
        "option3": "Must you return on today ?",
        "option4": "Must you return today ?",
        "question": "তোমাকে কি আজ ফিরতেই হবে ?",
        "correct": 4,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
        "option1": "Both of they have play well.",
        "option2": "They both have play well.",
        "option3": "Both they have to play well.",
        "option4": "Both of them have to play well.",
        "question": "তাদের দুজনকে ভালো খেলতেই হবে",
        "correct": 4,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
        "option1": "Sumati can not happy.",
        "option2": "Sumati can not be happy.",
        "option3": "Sumati may be not happy.",
        "option4": "Sumati can be not happy.",
        "question": "সুমতি খুশী হতে পারে না",
        "correct": 2,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
        "option1": "She may sad.",
        "option2": "She can sad.",
        "option3": "She may be sad.",
        "option4": "She can be sad.",
        "question": "সে (মেয়ে) দুঃখী হতেও পারে",
        "correct": 3,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
        "option1": "Should you not sorry ?",
        "option2": "Should sorry not you  be ?",
        "option3": "Should you have not be sorry ?",
        "option4": "Should you not be sorry ?",
        "question": "তোমার কি দুঃখিত হওয়া উচিৎ নয় ?",
        "correct": 4,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
        "option1": "He must be a good goalkeeper in future.",
        "option2": "He must good goalkeeper in future.",
        "option3": "A good goalkeeper must him in future.",
        "option4": "He is must be a good goalkeeper in future.",
        "question": "সে ভবিষ্যতে ভালো গোলকীপার হতে বাধ্য",
        "correct": 1,
    "isPicture": false
    }
]